# Vitalii Polianskyi (Full Stack Engineer)

**Skype:** vit.polyanskiy

E-mail: vit.polyanskiy@gmail.com

**Tel.:** +380 (99) 78- 36-817

Site: myfe.site

Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/polyanskiy-vitaliy/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/polyanskiy-vitaliy/</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/alreadyExisted">https://github.com/alreadyExisted</a>

## **Summary of qualifications:**

Front-end developer with a strong tech skill set and 5+ years of experience in the field of web-development.

Professional skills: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, RxJS, Node.js, Next.js, NestJS, PostgreSQL, Docker, WordPress, jQuery, HTML (Pug), CSS (SCSS, SASS, Stylus, PostCSS), Gulp, Grunt, Webpack, Git, Mercurial, Jira, Confluence.

Pet projects (low) skills: VueJS, GraphQL, MongoDB.

# **Experience:**

April 2020 - Present

Full Stack JS Developer at Technorely

**Position:** full-time web-developer.

## **Responsibilities:**

- Development of Single Page Applications, websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Code review.
- Estimate additional functionality.
- Interviewing new staff.
- Gave lectures on JavaScript for new employees.

## **Technologies and tools:**

TypeScript, React, Redux, NestJS, Objection.js, Puppeteer, PostgreSQL, Docker, HTML,

CSS (PostCSS), Webpack, Git, Figma, Jira, Confluence.

## October 2016 - April 2020 Full Stack JS Developer at Simcord LLC

**Position:** full-time web-developer.

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Development of Single Page Applications (SPA + SSR), websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Support of existing web APPs and sites.
- Code review.
- Estimate of new projects and additional functionality.
- Mentoring and training up junior and new staff.

#### **Technologies and tools:**

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Next.js, RxJS, Node.js, Recharts, D3, WebSockets, PostgreSQL, Docker, HTML, CSS (PostCSS, SCSS, SASS, Stylus), Gulp, Webpack, Git, Mercurial, Photoshop, Jira, Confluence.

Aug. 2015 – Sep. 2016 Web-developer at Startup

**Position:** remote full-time web-developer.

## Responsibilities:

- Development of websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Support of existing web sites.

## **Technologies and tools:**

JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, HTML, CSS, SASS, Twitter Bootstrap, Gulp, Git, Photoshop.

## Languages

English – Pre-Intermediate.

Ukrainian – native.

Russian – native.

#### Education

• 2010 - 2015, H.S. Skovoroda Kharkiv National Pedagogical University, obtained Master's degree in Physics, Computer Science.

#### **Additional information**

I've released in production over 30 websites.

I have experience in developing web applications (SPA + SSR) using such JavaScript frameworks as React, Next.js, NestJS, Express.

Creation of code that is valid, cross-browser, rubber, and adaptive to different screen resolutions. Ability to work both in a team and independently. Purposeful, self-motivated, and sociable, able to work within strict deadlines, and think outside the box. I seek to constantly enhance my professional skills and adopt new practices that can benefit the quality of my work.